<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quick Doc</string>
    <string name="dcSpec">Speciality : </string>
    <string name="spec_1">Associate Consultant, Cardiology</string>
    <string name="dc_degree">MBBS, D Card (Nairobi),Msc Cardiology (KE)</string>
    <string name="dc_phn_1">0102030405</string>
    <string name="dc_email_1">info@daktariwako.com</string>

    <string-array name="department_names_array">
        <item>Emergency</item>
        <item>Medicine</item>
        <item>Neuromedicine</item>
        <item>Physical Medicine</item>
        <item>Surgery</item>
        <item>Neurosugery</item>
        <item>Paediatric Surg</item>
        <item>Othopedic Surg</item>
        <item>Burn Plastic</item>
        <item>Dermatology</item>
        <item>Nephrology</item>
        <item>Psychiatry</item>
        <item>Cardiology</item>
        <item>Paediatrics</item>
        <item>Medical Oncology</item>
        <item>Gastroenterology</item>
        <item>Radiology</item>
        <item>Anesthesiology</item>
        <item>Traumatologyv</item>
        <item>Urology</item>
        <item>Ophthalmology</item>
        <item>Gynae</item>
        <item>Transfusion Med</item>
        <item>Paediatric Nephrology</item>
        <item>Hepatology</item>
        <item>Neurology</item>
        <item>Dentistry</item>
        <item>Oral Surgery</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="emergency_list_array">
        <item>Help Desk: 0102030405</item>
        <item>Medicine: 0102030405</item>
        <item>Emergency: 0102030405</item>
        <item>Ambulance 1: 0102030405</item>
        <item>Ambulance 2: 0102030405</item>
        <item>ICU services: 0102030405</item>
        <item>Critical Care: 0102030405</item>
        <item>Administration: 0102030405</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tips_array">
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt;Practice Exercise:.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            Learn to wake up every day to practice exercise. It increases your digestive energy and eases back pain. It also helps in regular routine, more energy, better mood, better sleep, lower blood pressure, less stress etc.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt;Brush daily:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            Many people do not know how to brush their teeth according to the rules. As much damage to the teeth and gums as a result of brushing incorrectly can be the reason for not brushing at all. Lots of people don’t brush enough, don’t flush and talk to a dentist regularly if necessary and brush for at least two minutes.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt;Eat foods rich in vitamin C:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            We need at least 90 mg of vitamin C every day. The best way to get this is to serve at least five fresh fruits and vegetables a day. Try eating oranges and guavas.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt;Take vitamin A: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            Vitamin A and beta carotene help to increase immunity against the disease. It helps in curing diseases like measles and is recommended by WHO.
            Natural sources of vitamin A are kidney, liver, dairy products, green and yellow vegetables, papaya, mango, pepper, red sorrel and red palm oil.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt;Drink pure water:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
            Do not drink soft drinks or energy drinks while exercising. Stay properly hydrated by drinking enough water during your work.
        </item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="faqs_array">
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt; 1. Can appointments be tracked? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

            &lt;b&gt;Answer: &lt;/b&gt; Yes, you can track your appointments. You can watch your serial by going to the Track Appointments tab and selecting the doctor who made the appointment under you and selecting the given date and time.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt; 2. Will I need any money to use this app? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

            &lt;b&gt;Answer: &lt;/b&gt; No, this app can be used for free.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt; 3. Can all hospital doctors appointments be available here? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

            &lt;b&gt;Answer: &lt;/b&gt; No, the app is centered on only one hospital, so only doctor appointments can be made here.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt; 4. Can I see an appointment without login? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

            &lt;b&gt;Answer: &lt;/b&gt; Yes, it can be seen. Keeping in mind the convenience of everyone, the app has been kept free of login.
        </item>
        <item>
            &lt;b&gt; 5. Can feedback be given in the app? &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;

            &lt;b&gt;Answers &lt;/b&gt; Answers can be given and you can also see the feedback given to other doctors.
        </item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
